mortalonline.com 2019-10-16

# Privacy Policy — Mortal Online

**What is a privacy policy?**  
We collect personal information from you as you use mortalonline.com,account.mortalonline.com,support.mortalonline.com.

Our privacy policy applies to ALL of our websites, whether you access them through a web browser, a mobile app, or another way. Our privacy policy does NOT apply to information collected on you by someone else. In those cases, you should consult that person’s privacy policy.

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address.

We collect technical data when you login to your account in Mortal Online or the forums such as IP address and web browser information.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

• To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

• To help support verify who you are.  
If you need to contact our support to get help with a account issue, support will at times use this information to verify who you are.

• Law, protection, or the public good.  
We can also use your personal information to comply with our legal obligations, protect the vital interests of our users, and as needed for the public good. This may include using your personal information to prevent and handle potential fraud, security breaches or other prohibited activities.

• By contract.  
A contract also creates a basis for using your information. By accepting our Terms of Service, a contract is formed between us and you so that we may provide you our services. We can use your personal information as needed to provide our services to you under that contract.

 **How long do you store my information?**  
If you have an account, we will store your personal information indefinitely.  
Generally, if you delete your account, we will continue to store your personal information for a short time in case of any issues, and then we will delete it in accordance with our standard procedures and applicable law. However, for security purposes, we continue to store your technical data for up to eighteen (18) months after your account deletion.

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

These security measures include: SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the \’Edit Profile\’ page.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

 **How do I change or delete my information?**  
You can update some types of information directly within your account settings. If you are unable to change your information within your account settings, please contact us and we will attempt to make the required changes. To protect your privacy and security, we may require you to take certain steps or provide additional information to verify your identity before we provide any information or make corrections. It’s important to remember that if you delete or limit the use of your information, our services may not function properly.  
You can withdraw your consent at any time. Please contact us if you would like to revoke your prior consent to any of these uses.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms of Service**  
Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.mortalonline.com/TOS.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Who can I contact with questions?**  
If you have any questions about your information or our privacy policy, or if you would like to make a complaint about how Star Vault AB processes your information, please contact us by using the details below:

Data Controller:  
Star Vault AB  
Drottninggatan 38  
Sweden, Malmoe 211 41  
info@starvault.se

Data Protection Officer:  
Star Vault AB  
Drottninggatan 38  
Sweden, Malmoe 211 41  
info@starvault.se
